What's going on?
Is something about to start?
Meganii!
Ta-da!
The Dream Theatre is ready!
And to commemorate this event,
an unveiling concert will be held!
Awesome!
So they finally finished it?
Have all of you formed your five person teams?
What?!
Nope.
Not yet!
What's this? How unfortunate...
Then how about this...
The team that wins tomorrow's sports festival
will get to put on a special concert.
The team that wins tomorrow's sports festival?
We're having a sports festival?
Can we have as many people as we wantko?
Yes.
However, the condition is that you
must show me your glistening sweat.
We'd love to participate!
Chanko!
Kyupikon!
I'm glad.
Now then, let us meet again tomorrow.
It'd be nice if we could participate.
Huh? We're not?
Are you dense or something, Laala?
We haven't reformed yet.
Uh...
Even if we entered the sports festival and managed to win...
we wouldn't be able to perform as a team.
Pshuu...
We can thank them for that.
Yeah.
Let's participate anyways.
Huh?
But...
I have an idea.
What is it? Whatcha got?! Out with it!
What do you have in mind-pri?
First to the Dream Theatre-kuma!
Kuma!
Let's make a bet-pri!
Kuma?!
If we manage to win the sports festival,
you'll bare witness to our ritual-pri.
SoLaMi SMILE will reform-pri!
Say what?!
You're asking too much!
I'll be cursed if I do that!
Like I told you, it ain't happening!
Don't enter the sports festival!
If by chance you girls win...
Then be cursed-pri.
No, not that!
Besides, curses don't exist-pri.
We're doing everything we can for our team.
You're also part of our team, Kuma.
Ah! Hold on a moment-kuma!
Hold on-usa!
As if!
Better prepare yourself for the worst.
But...
Hold on-kuma!
Watch where you're flying-usa!
So you're in the same situation-kuma?
You too-usa?
Though, there's nothing to worry about-usa.
They won't win that easily-usa.
I'll be fine-kuma.
They've got Sophy on their team-kuma.
What the hell-kuma?!
I'm a manager, you know-kuma!
What should I do-usa?!
That's enough, you idiot!
It's heart-breaking-usa!
Neko~n.
It's finally starting!
The sports festival will be starting shortly.
All those participating, please gather up.
Okay!
We're already in line.
Pri!
Capisce!
Okay~.
Go!
Max!
Relax.
The prophecy has changed since last week.
Prophecy Grimoire, chapter 13, section 32:
"Those who have been defeated when the angel descends shall weep in frustration."
Leave the sports festival to me!
I shall have Manaka Laala bow down to us when we win!
Welcome to the "All Idol Grand Sports Festival",
where all of our idols are trying to win the prestigious...
...Dream Theatre Special Unveiling Concert!
There truly are a lot of idol teams participating.
If you were to walk your dog, he'd likely bump into an idol.
W-Woof!
Huh?
Anyway, aim to be number one,
and claim the right to have a truly once in a lifetime unveiling concert!
Our first event is an obstacle course.
Please choose one member from your team to compete.
That'll be me.
I've been practicing my swinging, so I've got this.
And I've been doing ninja training every day.
Right, Reona?
Yeah.
While in the bath.
That'll be a problem.
Why?!
I'll do it.
Presentation is what's important, you know!
Let's leave this one to Laala-pri.
I like races, so caprace!
Start!
Dorothy, you dirty trickster!
Dorothy!
If I win, you won't have a problem with it, right?
Teams who haven't started are disqualified.
Kyupikon!
Those who go off the path are also disqualified.
Capisce!
Chanko!
We who have been reborn from the ancient darkness...
...entrust that thee shall bring us victory, Mikan!
Demon Demon Deruderu Beam!
I've got this one covered!
I'm off!
Oh, box vaulting!
My specialityko!
Capisce!
Gel!
What?!
That's some skill, Mikan!
Gel!
Mikan is super nimble-pri.
She's in shape.
Gel-gel!
I'm at a loss for words.
Even though Mikan had a late start,
she managed to pass everyone and has taken the lead by showing off her extraordinary reflexes.
She's amazing!
No way...
Your next obstacle is an eating contest.
I'm glad I skipped out on breakfast!
Man, there's onions and shichimi in this.
Chanko!
I'm so glad there's so much!
What a heated battle!
It feels great when you can eat all you want.
Chanko.
Chanko!
Gelruru!
Even though she only needed one,
Mikan managed to stack up three huge piles!
And now...
First place!
No mortal can beat Mikan when in eating or sports.
Aromageddon shall be victorious.
It would be best if you realize how truly fearsome we are.
My, you sure are full of yourself.
That was so impressive, Mikan!
Thankies!
I shall bless you, too.
With the way things are going, SoLaMi SMILE will lose,
which means I don't need to worry about being cursed.
Same here.
Well of course.
Aromageddon has a huge lead.
Our second event is...
a limbo competition!
After running, jumping, and eating
comes passing under, right?
The top four teams will battle it out.
Huh?
This is a sports festival?
They're going all out.
There are only four teams left.
First up, Sion. I got this!
Let me go!
Let's Go!
Sion is the first to clear it!
You're up next, Mikan!
Gel!
Gelruru!
Gel.
A perfect 10-gel!
My dear, have you by chance
confused this with the high jump?
Huh?
Unfortunately, you've been disqualified.
Really?!
Our next contestant is...
Another disqualification.
Sadako!
Chanko!
Pshuu...
Sophy shows off her splendid flexibility earning her an impressive score.
As it currently stands, the teams with the most points and tied for first are Aromageddon and SoLaMi SMILE.
Dressing Pafé comes in third,
and unfortunately, Team Sadako has been eliminated.
Hooray!
We have one event left in the competition.
But before that, we'll take a commercial break.
Our final event is the three-legged race,
or for some, the four-legged race up the mountain.
They're going all out-pri.
Mountain climbing, huh?
This requires teamwork.
In other words, it's a competition that
will test the strength of one's friendship.
That's right.
And the team that wins...
will be given 10,000 points!
Gel?!
If we lose, we'll suddenly drop from the top?
What?
That's sneaky!
That coming from a demon-pri?
This is common in PriPara-pri.
We shall not lose to the likes of ye!
After all, the black flames of hell shall wrap themselves around ye.
Gel!
Huh?
Eh?
Something smells fishy-pri.
Saury...
Bonfires aren't allowed here.
Nekon...
Those who have inhaled this smoke shall fall to my magic.
Therefore, you shall all lose!
Unfortunately for you, I held my breath.
No one would actually inhale in the smoke, would they?
Of course not-pri.
I inhaled it!
Huh?!
Now you're cursed!
Start!
Sorry.
The smoke upset my stomach.
Let's synchronise on white, black, white!
White, black.
Faster, Aroma.
Go on without me, Mikan.
No way. We're doing it together.
White, black.
Gel! Gel! Gel!
Laala, you all right-pri?
What do we do?
We're in dead last.
Take a deep breath.
A complete capisce!
You can do it!
All right, let's turn this around-pri!
Go for it!
Pri! Pri!
Capisce!
Pushuu~.
Pri! Pri!
Capisce!
Pushuu~.
We're pushing so no pushuu~ing!!
Capisce!
Pri! Pri!
Nice rhythm-pri
Nice rhythm.
There's no way SoLaMi SMILE will win-nekon.
Or so I thought! They're gaining-nekon!
How annoying-nekon!
I guess I'll have to...
Pri! Pri!
Capisce!
Hey, Kuma.
Oh, Neko-neesan.
I don't want you to go bald.
So stop those girls right away-nekon.
Pre-tty pl-ease.
Capikuma!
Capisce!
Hold on! The curse! Don't forget the curse!
Kuma?
Pushuu~.
Sophy!
I fear she's reached her limit-pri.
Pull yourself together, Sophy.
S-Sophy...
Sophy, go ahead and use us for support.
But...
That's how teams win-pri!
Yeah.
You share your problems with everyone.
And with that, you become one in both body and soul-pri.
Okay!
Pri! Pri!
Capisce!
Capi-
Aroma, are you okay?
Devi...
That's it.
Demons aren't used to running-devi.
This is our chance!
Aroma crashed and burned.
But Dressing Pafé are so far ahead.
Gel...
Gel...?
According to my calculations,
we have a 0.02% probability of winning-pri.
Probability? What?
I haven't learned about that yet.
Then stop.
It's already over-kuma.
I won't...
Sophy....
Sophy!
...give up either.
I want to perform!
Pri! Pri!
Capisce!
You girls...
Pri! Pri!
Capisce!
It's 10,000 years too early for ye to surpass me.
Pri! Pri!
Capisce!
Keep it up!
Pri! Pri!
Capisce!
White, black.
Babes, if you win, the curse-
Out'ta the way!
Pri! Pri!
Capisce!
No way!
Get a move on!
Don't forget about our promise!
White, black.
Pri! Pri!
Capisce!
It's come down to a fight between
Dressing Parfait and SoLaMi SMILE!
And SoLaMi SMILE is slowly falling behind!
Capisce!
Pri! Pri!
I'm sorry... I'm so heavy.
Capisce!
We're almost there-pri!
I'm completely capisce!
It's all right-kuma!
You've done good enough-kuma!
It's pointless to push on-kuma.
If you work any harder, you'll end up collapsing-kuma!
Kumakuma, that's enough out of you-pri.
You're not giving up-kuma?
Do you want to perform that bad-kuma?
Well, I am a manager who's supposed to be getting them concerts...
I get it-kuma!
So what if I come down with a curse-kuma?
I'll just end up completely bald-kuma!
Okay, okay-kuma!
I got it-kuma!
Let's reform-kuma!
So what if I'm bald?!
I'm a man!
A man!
Really-pri?
Kuma!
Then the three of us... can perform!
Pri! Pri!
Capisce!
White, black.
Pri! Pri!
Capisce!
I'll break the tape!
As the centre, I'll do it!
Me!
I will!
I'll do it!
Hey!
I will!
Hooray!
Promise: Believe in friendship.
Rhythm: Carved in our hearts.
Paradise: Our goal.
We swear to stand on stage as one!
Don't look! Don't look-kuma!
You'll be shocked by how smooth I am-kuma!
What are you going on about-pri?
Huh?
My gorgeous locks-kuma!
Eh?!
Congrats on reforming.
SoLaMi SMILE won!
Dearest spectators,
you are welcome to take the subway from the TV station.
Now then, please proceed with the Dream Theatre Unveiling Concert.
However, even though you'll be performing at the Dream Theatre,
your concert routine will stay the same.
So this is where we scan in?
Yes.
Please form your Dream Team by scanning your Pri Tickets.
You can also scan each other's Friend Tickets.
Coord Change Start!
At last, the three members of SoLaMi SMILE have gathered,
and their matching coord is...
...a gentle and maidenly silhouette of spring in full bloom.
Sophy shows off her new appearance with chic and mysterious colours.
Dream Heart Race Coord!
Amazing!
A new stage-pri!
It's huge!
Hello everyone!
We're SoLaMi SMILE!
Please continue to support us!
Pri!
Making Drama Switch On!
Princess...
Where are you, Princess-kuma?!
Kuma?
Flower garden in full bloom!
For you!
Lovely Flower Cinderella!
Kuma!
Cyalume Change!
Amazing!
Chanko!
You've opened my eyes-kuma!
Your concert was beautiful-kuma!
I will never waver again-kuma!
SoLaMi SMILE is the best-kuma!
They're huge!
They're Dream Pri Tickets.
Thank you for that wonderful concert.
Now go out and find two more,
and show us a true Dream Theatre Concert with the five of you.
We will!
They beat us to the punch.
I know.
Let's try harder next time.
I shall grant the prophecy grimoire's baptism upon...
...the one who possesses both black and white as well as the imp with a clumsy heart.
Now that SoLaMi SMILE has reformed,
you're setting your sights on Sion and Dorothy?
Exactly.
Preposterous!
The first concert at the Dream Theatre has already been seized.
It's all your fault, Sion.
You just had to get in my way.
It's more your fault than mine.
You were the one who screwed up!
You!
Calm down, you two-usa.
Are you really fighting again-usa?
Come on, Reona, hurry up and stop them like you always do-usa.
Is it already the end for Dressing Pafé?
What?!
Next time:
Go! Farewell-usa?!
Aim for your dreams!
Let's go PriPara!